{
    "subject": "resource/Fury_at_Smugglers'_Bay",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Fury at Smugglers' Bay is a 1961 British adventure film produced, written and directed by John Gilling and starring Peter Cushing, Bernard Lee, Mich\u00e8le Mercier and John Fraser. The plot revolves around smuggling in Cornwall. Studio sequences were filmed at Twickenham Film Studios in west London with the external sequences representing the coast of Cornwall actually being shot at Abereiddy on the north Pembrokeshire coast in south-west Wales.",
    "human_readable": "Fury at Smugglers' Bay is a 1961 British adventure film that produced, wrote and directed by John Gilling and starring Peter Cushing, Bernard Lee, Mich\u00e8le Mercier and John Fraser.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9737482070922852,
            "question": "Who produced and wrote the film 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9708635807037354,
            "question": "Is 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay' a British film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9480921030044556,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9292123913764954,
            "question": "What is the title of the film starring Peter Cushing, Bernard Lee, Mich\u00e8le Mercier and John Fraser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.912204384803772,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9087300300598145,
            "question": "Besides directing, what other role did John Gilling have in 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8779297471046448,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8722918033599854,
            "question": "In what country was 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay' produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8269271850585938,
            "question": "Name one actor who starred in 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8107142448425293,
            "question": "Name two actors who appeared in 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay'."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fury at Smugglers' Bay is a 1961 British adventure film that produced, wrote and directed by John Gilling and starring Peter Cushing, Bernard Lee, Mich\u00e8le Mercier and John Fraser.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6656_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name one actor who starred in 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6656_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country was 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay' produced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6656_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Fury at Smugglers' Bay'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6656_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6656_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents provided mention that Fury at Smugglers' Bay is a 1961 British adventure film, and one of them even provides a detailed description of the film's production credits, which includes John Gilling as the producer, writer, and director, and Peter Cushing, Bernard Lee, Mich\u00e8le Mercier, and John Fraser as the main stars. Therefore, the information in the documents supports the triple, making the output \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information consistent with the statement that \"Fury at Smugglers' Bay\" is a 1961 British adventure film directed by John Gilling, produced by him, and written by him. The cast details for Peter Cushing, Bernard Lee, Mich\u00e8le Mercier, and John Fraser are also mentioned."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}